Faculty Women's Club. Scholarship files. 1985-1999.
UCLA Library Special Collections
Faculty Women's Club. Scholarship files.
1985-1999
University Archives Record Series 695
UCLA Library Special Collections
1.2 linear ft. (3 boxes)
Record Series 695 contains the scholarship files of UCLA's Faculty Women's Club. Files regard scholarship applications, reports, financial documentation, committees, publicity, winners, winners' dinners, and history.
Faculty Women's Club.
Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
Exception: application files are RESTRICTED and not open for research. For access, contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk.
Scope and Content
Record Series 695 contains the scholarship files of UCLA's Faculty Women's Club. Files regard scholarship applications, reports, financial documentation, committees, publicity, winners, winners' dinners, and history.
Application files are restricted and confidential.
This is an active record series; additional University records are expected to be added.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 4475135
- Scholarship - applications, confidential., 1985-1986. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Scholarship - correspondence., 1985-1986. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Scholarship - financial activity reports., 1985-1986. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Scholarship - correspondence., 1986-1987. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Scholarship - publicity., 1986-1987. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Scholarship - Clendenin donation bond., 1986-1987. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Scholarship - financial activity reports., 1986-1987. (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Scholarship - applications, confidential., 1987-1988. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Scholarship - winners., 1987-1988. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Scholarship - correspondence., 1987-1988. (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Scholarship - publicity., 1987-1988. (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Scholarship - donations., 1987-1988. (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Scholarship - financial activity reports., 1987-1988. (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Scholarship - deposit transmittal reports., 1987-1988. (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Scholarship - committee report (includes past reports)., 1987-1988. (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Scholarship - applications, confidential., 1988-1989. (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Scholarship - publicity., 1988-1989. (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Scholarship - financial activity reports., 1988-1989. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Scholarship - deposit transmittal reports., 1988-1989. (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Scholarship - applications, confidential., 1989-1990. (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Scholarship - financial activity reports., 1989-1990. (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Scholarship - deposit transmittal reports., 1989-1990. (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Scholarship - typesetting. (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Scholarship - applications, confidential., 1990-1991. (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Scholarship - correspondence., 1990-1991. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Scholarship - winners' dinner., 1990-1991. (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Scholarship - contribution: David Miller., 1990-1991. (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Scholarship - financial activity reports., 1990-1991. (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Scholarship - deposit transmittal reports., 1990-1991. (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Scholarship - merging accounts., 1990-1991. (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Scholarship - applications, confidential., 1991-1992. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Scholarship - publicity., 1991-1992. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Scholarship - winners' dinner., 1991-1992. (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Scholarship - financial activity reports., 1992-1993. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Scholarship - correspondence., 1993-1994. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Scholarship - publicity., 1993-1994. (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Scholarship - miscellaneous., 1993-1994. (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Scholarship - financial activity reports., 1993-1994. (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Scholarship - deposit transmittal reports., 1993-1994. (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Scholarship - committee report (includes past reports)., 1993-1994. (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Scholarship - correspondence., 1994-1995. (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Scholarship - financial activity reports., 1994-1995. (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Scholarship - deposit transmittal reports., 1994-1995. (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Scholarship - committee report., 1994-1995. (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Scholarship - winners., 1994-1995. (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Scholarship - committee report., 1995-1996. (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Scholarship - correspondence., 1995-1996. (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Scholarship - financial activity reports., 1995-1996. (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Scholarship - committee report., 1996-1997. (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Scholarship - correspondence., 1996-1997. (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Scholarship - deposit transmittal reports., 1996-1997. (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Scholarship - financial activity reports., 1996-1997. (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Scholarship - job description and contacts., 1996-1997. (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Scholarship - publicity., 1996-1997. (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Scholarship - winners., 1996-1997. (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Scholarship - committee report., 1997-1998. (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Scholarship - correspondence., 1997-1998. (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Scholarship - deposit transmittal reports., 1997-1998. (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Scholarship - financial activity reports., 1997-1998. (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Scholarship - history (1918-1998)., 1997-1998. (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Scholarlship - job description and contacts., 1997-1998. (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Scholarship - winners., 1997-1998. (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Scholarship - committee report., 1998-1999. (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Scholarship - correspondence., 1998-1999. (Box 3, Folder 34)